

CONTACT ME

- bgsp_aditya@student.uns.ac.id
- www.bytadit.com
- @aditya-bagus-pratama
- www.github.com/bytadit

EDUCATION

Junior High School SMP N 9 Surakarta

2013 - 2016

Senior High School SMA N 1 Sukoharjo

2016 - 2019

S1 Informatics **Universitas Sebelas Maret** 2020 - present

LANGUAGES

Python SQL PHP Javascript HTML, CSS

English

C++

Aditya Bagus Pratama

servant of knowledge

PROFILE

A hard-working college student passionate about technology. I've worked as a lecturer assistant, as a team project manager, and as a participant in data-science bootcamp. I am interested in the implementation of data science and AI in search engine technology. I'm really excited about growing my skills and building my own portfolio by contributing to some open source projects.

EXPERIENCES

Secretary	2014- 2015
Student Council SMP Negeri 9 Surakarta	
Vice President	2017 - 2018
Red Cross Youth I SMA Negeri 1 Sukoharjo	
3rd Winner	2020 - 2021
ICEF 7 First Aid Competition I SMA Insan Cendekia	
Participant	2020 - 2021
Data Science Training I DQLab	
Lecturer Assistant	2021
Digital System I Universitas Sebelas Maret	

SKILLS

- · Problem-Solving
- Analytical Thinking
- Data Storytelling
- **Backend Coding**
- Leadership & Management
- **Public Speaking**